Pan is my rocket ship, taking me high
Into the stars, I’ll soar and fly
10... 9... feel the bass kick in
Escape velocity, the journey begins
Pan is my rocket ship, into the sky
Lifting my soul as the notes rise high
I hopped into my rocket, We're off to space
My smile’s so bright, like stars across my face
The pans are lined up, ready to go
Off to a planet, nobody else knows
When I land, it's something new
Every step, a melody comes through
A Pan planet under my feet,
Every step making sounds so sweet
Pan is my rocket ship, taking me high
Into the stars, I’ll soar and fly
10... 9... feel the bass kick in
Escape velocity, the journey begins
Pan is my rocket ship, into the sky
Lifting my soul as the notes rise high
As I journey onward, the ground beneath me sings
Footsteps spark a chorus, like the buzz of wings
Melodies envelop me, sweet as honey's gold
Echoes of "Bees' Melody" in stories untold
Pan is my rocket ship, taking me high
Into the stars, I’ll soar and fly
10... 9... feel the bass kick in
Escape velocity, the journey begins
Pan is my rocket ship, into the sky
Lifting my soul as the notes rise high
Now I'm back, learning to play
In Exodus band, day by day
The Pan I play, the sound so sweet
Feels like space under my feet
Pan is my rocket ship, taking me high
Into the stars, I’ll soar and fly
10... 9... feel the bass kick in
Escape velocity, the journey begins
Pan is my rocket ship, into the sky
Lifting my soul as the notes rise high